49% Motherf**ker, 51% Son of a Bitch
Lemmy is a music, documentary film directed by Wes Orshoski.
Over four decades, Motorhead frontman Lemmy  Kilmister has
registered an immeasurable impact on music history.
Nearly 65, he remains the living embodiment of the rock and roll lifestyle, and this feature-length documentary
tells his story, one of a hard-living rock icon who continues to enjoy the life of a man half his age.
Self, played by Lemmy Kilmister.
Self, played by Dave Brock.
Self, played by Phil Campbell.
Self, played by 'Fast' Eddie Clark.
Self, played by Jarvis Cocker.
Self, played by Alice Cooper.
Lemmy: 49% motherfucker.
51% son of a bitch.
is a 2010 documentary film profile of the English rock musician Ian "Lemmy" Kilmister,
the founder, bassist, and lead vocalist of the heavy metal band Motörhead.